monetizecoin.com 2018-09-13

# Monetize Coin: Privacy Policy

At MonetizeCoin.com, the privacy of our visitors is of great importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information collected by MonetizeCoin.com and how it is used.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at privacypolicy@monetizecoin.com

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, MonetizeCoin.com makes use of log files. Information that may be collected includes your Internet Protocol (IP) address, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the site, and gather demographic information. However, none of this data is linked to any information that can be used to identify you personally.

**Cookies**

This site uses cookies to store information about visitor preferences, to record user-specific information about which pages the user accesses or visits, and to customize webpage content based on the visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Advertising** Some of our advertising partners may use cookies on our site in order to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, and also to personalize the advertising content that you receive. The editors of this site do not have access to or control over cookies used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to such advertisers or web sites, and we cannot control their activities.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your browser’s options. More detailed information about managing cookies can be found at the website of your web browser.
